Welcome back, in this video we're going to have an introductions to types. So a very
欢迎回来，在这段视频中，我们将对类型进行介绍。所以一个非常
basic question to ask is what is a type anyway. And this question is worth asking
要问的基本问题是，到底什么是类型。这个问题值得一问。
because the notion of type, what a type is, does vary from programming language to
因为类型的概念，即类型是什么，确实随编程语言的不同而不同
programming language. Now roughly speaking the consensus is that a type is a set of
编程语言。粗略地说，现在的共识是类型是一组
values, and also, perhaps more importantly, a set of operations that are
值，或许更重要的是，还有一组操作，这些操作
unique to those values, a set of operations that are defined on those
对于这些值是唯一的，即在这些值上定义的一组操作
values. So, for example, if I looked at the type of integers, there are some
价值。举个例子，如果我看一下整数的类型，有一些
operations that you can do on integers. You can do things like, you can add. And
可以对整数执行的操作。你可以做这样的事情，你可以加法。和
you can subtract integers and you can compare integers whether they are greater
您可以减去整数，并且可以比较整数是否大于
than or equal or less than these operations are you know about numbers and
大于或等于或小于这些运算，你知道数字和
then there are operations on strings And strings are a different type. They have.
然后是对字符串的操作，字符串是不同类型的。他们已经做到了。
Operations like incantation and testing whether a string is, is an empty string or
诸如咒语和测试字符串是否为空字符串或
not And the other various variety of functions that are defined on strings. And
NOT和其他各种在字符串上定义的函数。和
the important thing that these operations are different from the operations defined
重要的是，这些操作与定义的操作不同
on integers and we don't want to mix them up. It would be bad if we started doing
我们不想把它们混为一谈。如果我们开始做这件事就不好了
string operations on integers for example. We would just get nonsense. So, in modern
例如，整数上的字符串操作。我们只会得到无稽之谈。所以，在现代
programming languages types are expressed in a number of different ways. In object
编程语言类型有多种不同的表示方式。在对象中
orient languages. Often we see classes being the notion of type. So, [inaudible]
东方语言。我们经常看到类是类型的概念。所以，[听不见]
in cool, the class names are the types, they're all, the, with one exception,
在Cool中，类名是类型，它们都是，除了一个例外，
called self type. The class names are exactly the types. And I just wanted to
叫做自我型。类名就是这些类型。我只是想要
point out that this need not be the case. It happens that it's often convenient in
指出事实并非如此。巧合的是，这通常是很方便的
[inaudible] Victorian languages to equate classes and types. But there are other
[听不见]维多利亚时期的语言，等同于等级和类型。但是还有其他的
designs that, where the classes are not the only kinds of types, or whether
设计，在类不是唯一类型的情况下，或者是否
they're. And in some languages, [inaudible] where there's no notion of
他们是。在一些语言中，[听不见]没有
class, the types are completely different things. So, classes and types are really
类中，类型是完全不同的东西。所以，类和类型实际上是
two different things that happen, to be identif ied in a lot of object oriented
在许多面向对象的领域中，会发生两件不同的事情
designs. And I just want you to be aware that that's not necessarily the only way
设计。我只想让你意识到这不一定是唯一的办法
to do it. So consider the assembly language fragment add R1 R2 R3 and what
去做这件事。那么考虑一下汇编语言片段add R1、R2、R3等等
does this actually do. Well it takes the contents of register R2 and the contents
这真的能做到吗。它取寄存器r2的内容和
of register R3 it adds them together, and it puts the results in register R1. And
将它们相加，并将结果放入寄存器r1。和
the question is, what are the types of R1 R2 and R3 And you might hope that they're
问题是，R1、R2和R3的类型是什么，您可能希望它们是
integers but in fact this is a, this is a trick question Because at the assembly
整数，但实际上这是一个，这是一个刁钻的问题，因为在汇编
language level I can't tell. There's nothing that prevents R1, R2, and R3 from
语言水平我说不清。没有什么可以阻止R1、R2和R3
having arbitrary types. They could be, they could be representatives of any kind
具有任意类型的。他们可以是，他们可以是任何形式的代表
of type and because they're just a bunch of registers with zero and 1's in them the
类型，因为它们只是一堆带有0和1的寄存器，
add operation will be happy to take them and add them up even if it doesn't make
添加操作会很乐意接受它们并将它们相加，即使它不会
sense And produce a bit pattern that then stores into R1. So, to make this a little
检测并产生位模式，然后将其存储到R1中。所以，为了让这件事变得有点
clear perhaps it's useful to think about a, a certain operations that are legal for
显然，考虑一种，一种特定的操作是合法的，也许是有用的
values of each type. So for example, it make perfect example to add two integers,
每种类型的值。因此，例如，将两个整数相加是一个完美示例，
if I have two bit patterns that represent integers, then when I sum them up I would
如果我有两个表示整数的位模式，那么当我将它们相加时，我会
get a bit pattern that represents the sum of those two integers. But on the other
获取表示这两个整数之和的位模式。但另一方面
hand, if I take a function pointer and integer and I add them together, I really
另一方面，如果我把函数指针和整数加在一起，我真的
don't get anything. Okay this is another the function pointer is a bit pattern. The
什么都没拿到。好的，这是另一个，函数指针是位模式。这个
imaginer s a bit pattern I can take those two bit patterns. I could run them through
想象一下，这是一个位模式，我可以取这两个位模式。我可以把它们穿过去
and I do get out a new set of bits. But there's no useful interpretation of that
我确实拿出了一组新的比特。但对此没有什么有用的解释
results. The resulting things I get doesn't mean anything, but the problem is
结果。我得到的结果没有任何意义，但问题是
that these both have the same assembly language implementation. Okay, nothing at
它们都有相同的汇编语言实现。好的，没什么
the assembly language level, these two operations look exactly the same. So I
在汇编语言级别，这两个操作看起来完全一样。所以我
can't tell at the assembly language level, which one of these I'm doing. If I want
在汇编语言级别我不知道我在做哪一个。如果我想的话
there to be types, if I want to make sure that I only do operations on the correct,
有一些类型，如果我想确保我只对正确的
that I only do certain operations on, on their correc t types, then I need some
我只在他们的相应类型上做一些特定的操作，那么我需要一些
sort of type description, some sort of type system to enforce those distinctions.
某种类型描述，某种类型系统来加强这些区别。
Perhaps I'm belaboring this point, but I think it's important, so one more time. A
也许我在重复这一点，但我认为这很重要，所以再说一次。一个
languages type system specifies which operations are valid for which types. Then
语言类型系统指定哪些操作对哪些类型有效。然后
the goal for type checking is to ensure that operations are used only, only with
类型检查的目标是确保操作仅用于
the correct types. And by doing this, type checking enforces the intended
正确的类型。通过这样做，类型检查强制执行预期的
interpretation of values because nothing else is going to check. Once we get to the
对价值的解释，因为没有其他东西会被检查。一旦我们到了
machine code level, it's all just a lot of 0's and 1's, and the machine will be happy
机器代码级别，这只是一大堆0和1，机器会很高兴的
to do whatever operations we tell it to on those 0's and 1's, whether or not those
在那两个0和1上做我们告诉它的任何操作，不管是不是那些
operations make sense. So the purpose of type systems is to enforce the intended
运营是有意义的。因此，类型系统的目的是强制执行预期的
interpretations of those bit patterns and make sure that if I have a bit pattern for
这些位模式的解释，并确保如果我有一个位模式
integers that I don't do any non-integer operations on that and get something that
整数，我不对它做任何非整数运算，然后得到一些
is meaningless. Today, programming languages fall into three different
是没有意义的。今天，编程语言分为三种不同的类型
categories with respect to how they treat types. There are the statically types
类别与其处理类型的方式相关。有静态类型
languages, where all, or almost all, of the checking of types is done as part of
语言，其中所有或几乎所有类型检查都是作为
compilation, and Cool is one of these And other languages that you've probably seen,
编译，Cool是你们可能见过的这些和其他语言中的一种，
like C and Java, are also statically typed. Then there are the dynamically
与C和Java一样，也是静态类型的。然后是动态的
typed languages, where almost all of the checking of types is done as part of
类型化语言，其中几乎所有的类型检查都是作为
program execution. And the Lisp family of languages, like Scheme and Lisp itself,
程序执行。还有Lisp语言家族，比如Scheme和Lisp本身，
are in this category, as are languages like Python And pearl So you've probably
和Python和PEPEL这样的语言一样属于这一类，所以您可能已经
used, or heard of, at least, some of those languages And finally there are the
使用或听说过这些语言中的一部分，最后还有
un-typed languages where no type checking is done at all, either at compile time or
完全不进行类型检查的非类型化语言，无论是在编译时还是在
at run time. And this is basically what machine code does. So machine code has no
在运行时。这基本上就是机器代码所做的事情。所以机器代码没有
notion of types and it forces no extraction boundaries, when it executes.
类型的概念，并且它在执行时不强制任何提取边界。
For decades there has been debate about the relative merits of static versus
几十年来，关于静电和
dynamic typing and without taking sides let me lay out for you what the various
动态打字，不偏袒任何一方，让我为您展示一下各种
proponents on each side say. So, the people who believe in static typing say,
双方的支持者都表示。所以，相信静电打字的人说，
that static checking catches many programming errors in compile time and it
静电检查在编译时捕获了许多编程错误，并且它
also avoids the overhead of runtime type checks. If I hooked on all the type
还避免了运行时类型检查的开销。如果我迷上了所有类型的人
checking and compiled time well I don't have to check the types at runtime. I
检查和编译时间很好，我不必在运行时检查类型。我
don't have to check when I go do an operation that the arguments are of the
在我执行操作时，不必检查参数是否属于
correct type because I already that check once and for all in compile time. And
正确的类型，因为我已经在编译时一劳永逸地检查了。和
these things are both definitely true. These are the two big advantages of static
这两件事都是千真万确的。这是静电的两大优势
checking. First of all Proves that some errors can never happen those are caught
正在检查。首先证明有些错误是永远不会发生的
at compile time so I never have to worry about those errors at run time, and its
这样我就不必担心运行时的那些错误了，而且它的
faster Dynamic typing proponents counter that aesthetic type systems are
更快动态打字的支持者反驳说，美观的打字系统
restrictive. So essentially, aesthetic type system has to prove that the program
有限制性的。所以从本质上说，美学类型系统必须证明程序
is well typed, that all the types makes sense And it does this by restricting what
是好类型的，所有类型都是有意义的，并且它通过限制
kinds of programs you can write. There are some programs that are more difficult to
你可以写的各种程序。有一些程序更难
write in an aesthetic type language because the compiler has a hard time
用美观的类型语言编写，因为编译器很难
proving them correct. And there's also a belief that I, I see commonly stated that
证明他们是正确的。还有一种观点认为我，我看到通常都会说
rapid prototyping is more difficult with ecstatic type system. I think the idea
对于欣喜若狂的类型系统，快速成型更加困难。我认为这个想法
here is that if you're prototyping something, if you're exploring some idea
这就是如果你在制作某样东西的原型，如果你在探索一些想法
you may not actually know exactly what all the types are at that point in time And
在那个时间点上，您可能并不确切地知道所有类型是什么，
having to commit to something that is going to work in all cases. You know, to
必须致力于在所有情况下都能奏效的事情。你知道，为了
having a type correct program when you're just trying to fiddle around and figure
有一个正确的程序，当你只是想要摆弄和计算的时候
out what it is you're trying to do. That's very constraining and makes the work go
弄清楚你到底想做什么。这是非常有约束力的，并使工作得以进行。
quite a bit slower. So what's the actual situation and practice today? Well, an
慢了点。那么今天的实际情况和实践是什么呢？那么，一个
awful lot of code is written in [inaudible] type languages. And the
很多代码都是用[听不见]类型的语言编写的。以及
practical [inaudible] type languages that people use a lot have always have some
人们经常使用的实用的[听不见的]类型的语言总是有一些
kind of escape mechanism. So, in C, in Java, in C++, you have some notion of
一种逃生机制。因此，在C、Java、C++中，您都有一些概念
unsafe cast. In C an unsafe cast can just results in a runtime crash. In Java it r
不安全的演员阵容。在C语言中，不安全的强制转换只会导致运行时崩溃。在Java中，它是
esults in an [inaudible] runtime, when you have an unsafe or failed downcast. But
当您有不安全或失败的向下转换时，会在[听不见]运行时产生结果。但
the, the effect is that you can get run time errors for type reasons. [sound] Now
其效果是，由于类型原因，您可能会得到运行时错误。[声音]现在
on the dynamic typing site, the people who programming dynamic languages, they always
在动态打字网站上，编写动态语言的人总是
end up or seemed end up record fitting static typing to these dynamically typed
最终或似乎最终记录适合静电打字到这些动态键入
languages. So typically if a dynamically typed language because popular enough than
语言。所以通常情况下，如果动态类型的语言足够流行，
people trying to write optimizing compilers for them and the first thing
人们试图为它们编写优化编译器，首先要做的就是
that people want to have on an optimizing compiler. Is some insta, type information
这是人们希望在优化编译器上拥有的。是一些实例、类型信息
because it helps to generate much better code? And so people wind up going back and
因为它有助于生成更好的代码？所以人们最终回到了过去，
trying to figure out how to get as many types as they can from these dynamically
试图找出如何从这些动态地获取尽可能多的类型
types languages as soon as they start trying to build serious tools to improve
在语言开始尝试构建严肃的工具以改进时，立即键入语言
the programs written in these languages. And in my opinion it's really debatable
用这些语言编写的程序。在我看来，这真的是值得商榷的
whether either compromise because, both of these are compromises on the either strict
是不是妥协，因为，这两个都是妥协，不是严格的
static or strict dynamic point of view. But if either one of these represents the
静电还是严格的动态观点。但如果这两个选项中的任何一个代表
best or the worst of both worlds. But this is certainly where we are today in
这两个世界要么是最好的，要么是最坏的。但这肯定是我们今天所处的位置
practice. Now Cool is a statically typed language and the types that are available
练习一下。现在Cool是一种静态类型的语言，
in Cool are the class names, so every time you define a class you define a new type,
Cool中是类名，所以每次定义类时都会定义一个新类型，
and the special reserve symbol SELF'lt;u>TYPE which we'll be talking about in a separate'lt;/u>
和特殊保留符号self‘lt；u>类型，我们将在单独的’lt；/u>类型中讨论
video all of its own. And the way cool works is that the user declares the types
所有的视频都是它自己的。Cool的工作方式是用户声明类型
for identifiers. For every identifier you have to say what its type is But then the
用于标识符。对于每个标识符，您必须说明其类型，但是
compiler does the rest of the work. The compiler refers the type for expressions.
编译器负责睡觉的工作。编译器引用表达式的类型。
And in particular the compiler assigns a type to every single expression in, in the
尤其是，编译器会为、中的每个单个表达式分配一个类型。
program. So it will go through the entire abstract syntax string and using the
程序。因此它将遍历整个抽象语法字符串，并使用
declared types for identifiers it will calculate a type for every expression and
标识符的声明类型，它将计算每个表达式的类型，并且
sub-expression. To wrap up, it's worth mentioning that there's a couple of
子表达式。最后，值得一提的是，有几个
different terms people use for the process of computer types, and that they mean
人们使用不同的术语来描述计算机类型的过程，它们的意思是
slight ly different things. So the simpler problem is what is known as type checking.
略有不同的东西。所以更简单的问题是所谓的类型检查。
Here, we have a fully typed program, meaning we have an abstract syntax, free
在这里，我们有一个完全类型化的程序，这意味着我们有一个抽象的语法，FREE
with all the types filled in on every node, and our only job is to check. That
每个节点都填写了所有类型，我们唯一的工作就是检查。那
the types are correct, so we can just look at each note and its neighbors and confirm
类型是正确的，所以我们只需查看每个音符及其邻居，然后确认
that the types are correct in that part of the tree. And we can do this for every
树的该部分中的类型是正确的。我们可以为每一个人做这件事
part of the tree and check that the Program is type correct. Type inference,
部分诊断树，并检查程序类型是否正确。类型推理，
on the other hand, is the process of filling in missing type information. So
另一方面，是填充缺失类型信息的过程。所以
here the view is that we have an abstract syntax tree with no types on it, or
这里的视图是，我们有一个没有类型的抽象语法树，或者
perhaps just a few types in key locations, on say, on the declared variables, and
也许只有几个关键位置的类型，比如说，声明的变量上的类型，以及
then we want to fill in missing types. We have some nodes in there, there with
然后我们想要填充缺少的类型。我们在那里有一些节点，那里有
absolutely no type information at all, and it's not just a question of confirming or
完全没有类型信息，这不仅仅是确认或
checking that the types are correct, we actually have to fill in the missing type
检查类型是否正确，我们实际上必须填充缺少的类型
information. And these two things are different. Actually there are many
信息。这两件事是不同的。实际上有很多
languages that are actually very, very different, but people often use the terms
实际上非常、非常不同的语言，但人们经常使用这些术语
interchangeably, and will not be particularly careful in my videos about
可以互换，在我的视频中不会特别小心
which term I am using either.
这两个词我都用了。